Finding aid for the Henry A. Waxman papers LSC.2261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Committee Files, (1971-2014, bulk 1995-2010); 1995-2010; (Boxes 1-233)
  - Committee on Oversight and Government Reform Files, undated (Box 206)
    Hubbell Tapes; Chung Background and Questions; Burton/Thompson Reports; Reno Hearing; Rep Delay Affidavit; Burton Subpoena/Confidential Information.
  - Committee on Oversight and Government Reform Files, undated (Box 207)
    Bush Administration Contacts with Enron; Background for Enron Hearing; Cheney Letters; Halliburton; GAO: Cheney; Homeland Security; Olympic Committee.
  - Committee on Oversight and Government Reform Minority Views, 2004-2007 (Box 30)
  - Committee on Oversight and Government Reform Rep. Waxman Chronological Files, 2008 Oct - Nov (Box 47)
  - Corrections Day, undated (Box 170)
    District Environment Issues; FDA; Prop 65 pre-emption.
  - Corrections Day File, undated (Box 182)
    HR 2343/ HR 2460; HR 2779; HR 3166.
  - Credit Rating Agencies, undated (Box 157)
    AGI, Lehman Brothers.
  - Department of Defense Correspondence, 2003 (Box 27)
  - Department of Defense Correspondence, undated (Box 32)
  - Dioxin Correspondence, undated (Box 173)
    Environment ?Things to Do? Folder; WTO Correspondence.
  - DMAA, undated (Box 109)
    USP labs response to information request on 1, 3-DMAA dietary ingredient; USP labs response to information request on 1, 3-DMAA dietary ingredient; DMAA-related correspondence; Guizhou study on geranium oil; Clintox Bioservices reports on maximum tolerated dosage
  - Drug Pricing/Nursing Home, undated (Box 131)
    NASA ?Fund? Issue; DOD Overseas Voting Investigation; Long Voting Lines; Drug Pricing: Press; Meeting notes; Research on drug pricing, coverage, affordability, usage; Legislation proposals; Interest group input; Nursing home staffing research & reports.
  - E&C, Medicare, AAA, Prostate, Chemo, undated (Box 184)
    Toys Correspondence; HPV Program.
  - Electricity Deregulation Files, 1988-1999 (Box 179)
    PUHCA Hearings ?88-?90; Clean Air Task Force; Waxman/Markey Letter.
  - Energy Bill, 2001-2002 (Box 169)
  - Energy Bill Files, 2001-2002 (Box 172)
    HR 4 Documents; HR 4 Press Releases; HR 4 Binder.
  - Energy Files (2001-2007) (Box 103)
    Talking points; HAW amendments; Energy conference amendments; H.R. 1649; Energy bill preemption report; Oil savings amendments; Energy bill & control issues; GAO reports; Waxman analyses.
  - Enron and California Energy Markets (Box 162)
  - Enron and Cheney Task Force, undated (Box 140)
  - EPACT, 2005-2006 (Box 167)
    Miscellaneous 2005; Carbon Neutral Government Gas Act.
  - EPACT 2005 Conference (Box 164)
    California Energy Crisis.
  - EPACT 2005 Conference (Box 165)
  - EPACT 2006 (Box 163)
    Enron; Clear skies; Climate.
  - Ethics Files, undated (Box 203)
    Ethics Waiver Prospect; Westar Energy Inc.; Karl Rove (Precedent, Letters, Statutes and Regulations); Ethic Waivers ? Background Research.
  - Executive Compensation, undated (Box 159)
  - Exhibits for Campaign Finance Investigation, 1997 (Box 110)
    Arnold, Truman 7/19/97; Castillo, Alejandra 8/19/97; Emerson, John 9/2/97; Lewin, Jim 8/21/97; Mills, Cheryl 11/3/97; Morris, Dick 8/21/97; Ryan, Evan 8/20/97; Sosnick, Doug 7/25/97. Weymouth, Holli 7/14/97.
  - Federal Spectrum, undated (Box 232)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. USF Data Request; Light Squared; Combat cellphone theft.
  - Financial Crisis overview, undated (Box 158)
    Regulators (Alan Greenspan).
  - Flavored Cigar Files, undated (Box 123)
    Flavored cigar document review materials & correspondence; Manufacturer internal sales & marketing documents; Tobacco notes; New Article
  - Food Quality Protection Act Files, undated (Box 180)
    Comm. Browner 5/15; Food Safety Advisory Committee; HR 3902.
  - GAO report on White House travel office operations, undated (Box 112)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. FBI General Counsel Report on Dissemination of FBI file information to HW; OPR report on FBI conduct; Talking points; Subpoenas & documents; Comparisons with and procedures of previous investigations (Iran-Contra, Iran-Bosnia, Whitewater, Watergate, October Surprise); Deposition authority factsheets & talking points; Abuse in Chairman Burton's Campaign finance investigation - deposition materials.
  - GHG rule, DOT lobbying, CEQ climate, Pedernales co-op, 2008 (Box 86)
    GHG rule; GHG rule request 3/12/08; Jason Burnett letter & interview; DOT lobbying; Letters to EPA & CEQ; DOT document productions; Interviews; Co-ops; Legislation; Documents; PEC documents.
  - GRID Act, 2009, 2011 (Box 91)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. CBO scoring issues, (sub) committee markups, bill draft; Pipeline safety bill (Pipeline Safety, Regulatory Certainty, and Job Creation Act of 2011); Bill draft, diluted bitumen study, free standards issue, (sub) committee notes; BP oil spill ? Blowout Prevention Act; 2009 climate bill (ACES).
  - HAW in the News and Hearing/Mark Up Coverage, 2009-2010 (Box 152)
  - HAW Profiles and HAW in the News, 2008-2009 (Box 150)
  - HAW Profiles and Press Coverage, 1980s-2010 (Box 139)
    HAW Profiles, Newsclips, and Quotes.
  - Health Reform-President?s Job?s Council, 2011 (Box 195)
  - House Contempt File history, undated (Box 229)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. 111th E&C Subpoenas; Toyota Subpoena; Committee Budget 106th; Resolution of inquiry.
  - HR 3514, undated (Box 186)
    HR 531; Freedom of Information Act.
  - HR2454 - ACES, undated. (Box 217)
  - Human Pesticide Testing, undated (Box 81)
    Aldicarb/Methomyl; Guthion; Oxamyl; Chloroprene/malathion
  - Human Pesticides Experiment Files, 2003 (Box 181)
    HAW Statements on Boxer-Waxman; 2003 Sign on Letters; 1/23/05 Pesticide Letter to Sen. Burns.
  - Inspector General Reports, 2008 (Box 39)
  - Investigation Files, undated (Box 193)
    Nursing Homes; Medicare prescription drug allowances; California Electric.
  - Iraq Contracts and Katrina contracts, undated (Box 80)
    Iraq contracts; CACI; Defense Energy Support Center; Altamia and Kellogg, Brown and Root (KBR); Katrina contracts; Carnival Cruise lines
  - LA Times/Chicago Tribune Spinoff, 2009-2014 (Box 190)
    Tobacco Tax and Regulation Loopholes.
  - Lead Water Meters (AWWA letter), undated (Box 174)
    Right to Know Clippings; HR 1636.
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 171)
    DeGette-Brown-Waxman Act; Propane 112(r ); Letter to clinical facilities.
  - Miscellaneous Work Product, undated (Box 122)
    Al-Arian, Sami Materials; Dolan, Jon Materials (Missouri legislator); Enron Tips; Jackson, Alphonso (HUD) Materials; Renal Drugs (Calcitriol) Materials and Legislation; Victory, Nancy Materials; White, Thomas Materials.
  - Navajo uranium contamination, 2007, 2008 (Box 89)
    EPA updates; Meeting notes; March 2008 5-year-plan draft; Legislative options; 10/23/07 Navajo uranium hearing.
  - News Clips and Hearing Coverage, 2009-2010 (Box 151)
    HAW in the News and Hearing/Mark Up Coverage.
  - News Clips on Halliburton, Iraqi Contracting, Abu Gharib, 2004-2005 (Box 146)
  - NFO, 1971-1990s (Box 213)
  - Nursing Home Files, 2000, 2003 (Box 95)
    Bush nursing home proposal; Copies of report, factsheets; Nursing home staffing bill (2003); Nursing home research materials; Nursing homes - reports - GAO, HCFA, other groups; Nursing home bill (2000).
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 74)
    Abuse report; GAO nursing data.
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 75)
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 76)
    GAO; Letter/reports; Statement of deficiency.
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 77)
    Statement of deficiency.
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 78)
    Data requests; correspondence reports; data press clippings.
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 79)
    Statement of deficiencies; incident reports; investigations; drafts; violations.
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 108)
    Staffing briefing/bill materials; Bill drafts and notes; Bill revisions; Abuse report & hearing materials; Abuse stories.
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 111)
    Staff notes; Nursing home statistics; Vet data; CMS Senior Analysis.
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 117)
    Illinois, NY, LA reports & other reports; Nursing home deficiency reports.
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 191)
  - Nursing Home Files, undated (Box 192)
  - Nursing Home Reports, 2003 (Box 94)
    Holt, Re. Rush; Lampson, Rep. Nick; Maloney, Rep. James; Mississippi (Rep. Bennie Thompson); Moore, Rep. Dennis; Norton Rep. Eleanor Holmes; Norton, Rep. Eleanor Holmes 2003 follow-up; Prisoners; Rodriguez, Rep. Ciro (Texas); Snyder, Rep. Vic; Stark, Rep. Fortney Pete; Thurman, Rep. Karen; Udall, Rep. Mark; Udall, Rep. Tom; Waxman correspondence; Waxman reports; Waxman report documents; Wexler, Rep. Robert; Wu, Rep. David.
  - Nursing Home Reports, undated (Box 96)
    Missouri; New York; Texas.
  - Nursing Home Reports, undated (Box 107)
    Carson, Rep. Brad; Bay Area reports (Reps. Stark, Eshoo, Lantos, Barbara Lee, Lofgren, George Miller, Pelosi, Tauscher, Woolsey); Berkley, Rep. Shelley; Capps, Rep. Lois; Chicago reports (Reps. Schakowsky, Rush, Blagojevich); Edwards, Rep. Chet; Forbes, Rep. Michael; Evans, Rep. Lane; Gephardt, Rep. Richard; DeGette, Rep. Diana; Filner, Rep. Bob; Clay, Rep. Lucy; Hoeffel, Rep. Joseph.
  - Nursing Homes and Lead Poisoning, 1991-2001 (Box 135)
    Legislation and GAO Reports.
  - 111th Congress Files, 2009-2010 (Box 218)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. ARRA; CFATS; HR 5626 ? BP; HR 5019 ? Home Star; HR 3795 & Other; FERC/CFTC bills; Other Bills/Topics.
  - Pesticide Files, undated (Box 176)
    Legislation; Interest Groups; Implementation.
  - Photo archive hard drive, undated (Box 233)
    Partial Restricted Access. Digitized HAW videos; Newsletters 1980- 1989; Video of the Mustache of Justice; Video of the Waxman Legacy; Photos on CDs of Waxman; Hard Drive of Electronic Committee Files; (files in the folder named ?Waxman Restricted Access UCLA Fil.
  - Pipeline safety, 2012, 2013 (Box 93)
    Subcommittee pipeline AINS; Spill notes/files (Enbridge-Marshall, MI; San Bruno; Chevron Salt Lake City; Exxon Yellowstone River); Pipeline Safety Act, Transportation & Infrastructure reauthorization testimony; Hydro bills; McMorris-Rodgers Hydropower Regulatory Efficiency Act (HR 267 of 2013); Murphy Collinsville Renewable Energy Promotion Act (HR 5625 of 2012); Title 17 ? No More Solyndras Act; Energy Efficiency; Building Star, Home Star, Rural Star.
  - Prescription Drugs, 1991-2001 (Box 136)
  - Press Clips for Reports and Selected Committee Coverage, 1999-2004 (Box 141)
  - Press Clips on Prescription Drug Pricing and HAW in the News, 1998-2000 (Box 143)
    Folders (HAW in the News) and Binders (Committee Member Coverage).
  - Press Clips on Prescription Drug Reform and Price Controls, 1998-2003 (Box 142)
    Selected Committee Member Coverage.
  - Press Coverage, 2007 (Box 148)
    Press Coverage of Investigations; ie Cheney Task Force, Tillman Hearing, Lynch Hearing.
  - Press Coverage, Assorted Letters, Hearing Memos, and Reports, undated (Box 144)
    Press Materials and News clips for Investigations; ie Mercury, Rx Drugs, Obesity.
  - Press Materials and News clips for Investigations on Abstinence, Drug Cards, and Energy Bill, undated (Box 145)
  - Press Office Activity, Monthly Record, 2008 (Box 149)
    AEY, Steroids, Fannie and Freddie.
  - Press on Steroids and Sports Investigations, Press Sign-in Sheets, and HAW in the News, 2005 (Box 147)
    Press Materials and Newsclips for Investigations; ie Medicaid, Medicare, Terri Shivo, Steroids in Sports.
  - Print Clips, 2011-2014 (Box 153)
  - Environment and climate documents, 1997-2008 (Box 219)
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
    Box contains one VHS tape entitled Climate Change: Unsettled Science.
  - Environment and global warming documents, 2005-2008 (Box 220)
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
    This box contains a Technology Advancement Office Clean Fuels Program 2007 Annual Report and 2008 Plan Update CD.
  - Tobacco legislation files, 1994-2003 (Box 221)
  - Tobacco hearings files, 1994-2000 (Box 222)
  - Tobacco subject files, 1983-2001 (Box 223)
  - Tobacco subject files, 1997-2001 (Box 224)
  - Tobacco subject files, 2001-2008 (Box 225)
  - Tobacco subject files, 1994-2000 (Box 226)
  - Tobacco investigation files and props, 1993-1998 (Box 227)
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL and AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Digital and audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
    Box contains one VHS and one CD-ROM.
  - Tobacco investigation files and props, 1994 (Box 228)
  - RX Drug Articles/Reports, undated (Box 212)
    President?s state by state Medicare info; Standard and Poor?s ? 97 Overview Report; Jama ? Is a gift just a gift?; Article Integrity; Media ethics info; Organization info; Reports Materials/Figures; Animal drug surveys; State population info; Press Clips by Category.
  - Safe Drinking Water Act Files, undated (Box 177)
    HR 2774; Bipartisan Letter & SDWA Statements; 1974 SOWA.
  - Senate climate bill, 2009, 2010 (Box 101)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. Senate climate bill; Offset summaries; ACES / K-B / S.1733 side-by-side (11/09); Kerry-Graham-Lieberman; ACES materials re floor; Talking points, support letters, amendments; REDD & offsets; Offsets; Offset enforcement; USCAP recommendations; Ben?s offset memo; Offset comments (6/10); Ag negotiations; Reports & background; Materials for negotiations; Senate Ag drafts; Kratovil letter; Bill background ? judicial review; Modeling; CBO, EPA, Business Roundtable modeling; Center for Climate Strategies; EIA draft & final States provisions / states? roles; Talking points committee markup; Hearing ? USCAP; Bill background; Market oversight, transportation, adaptation; Performance STNDS; USCAP comparison with ACES; Targets & timetables; Materials re discussion draft.
  - Seven - Member Rule Files, undated (Box 113)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. HAW v. Tommy Thompson case briefs; Waxman v. Evans Pleadings; Waxman v. Evans Misc.; 7-member rule requests reports.
  - Sign on Letters, 2001-2002 (Box 183)
  - Solyndra hearing binders, talking points, memos, undated (Box 189)
  - Staff notes on climate change (2008-2009) (Box 104)
  - Steroid Files, undated (Box 128)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. MLB arbitration records ? drug testing; MLB Joint Drug Prevention and Treatment Program documents Documents provided by the NFL; Rafael Palmeiro testing & report on investigation into committee testimony; High-schoolers Against Taking Steroids (HATS) letter; NCAA study of college athlete substance use.
  - Steroid Interviews, 2008-2009 (Box 133)
    scope and Content
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. Scott Shannon 1-31- 08; Dr. Taylor 2-4-08; Andy Pettitte 2-4-08; Melvin Craig 2-4-08; William Clemens 2-5-08; Brian McNamee 2-7-08; Rex Jones 2-8-08; David LaBossiere 2-8-08; Chuck Knoblauch 2-1- 08; David Littner 2-11-08; Alan Gross 2-11-08; Eugene Monahan 2-12-08; Lilian Straim 2- 12-08; Arthur Pappas 2-12-08; GM and Chrysler Dealership Closures and Restructuring: Hearing transcript 6-12-09; Additional dealer contributions to hearing.
  - Steroids Baseball Documents Provided by MLB, undated (Box 127)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. Testing & collective bargaining agreements; Commissioners? memos on drug policy and prevention programs; Memos & information on baseball drug education and prevention programs; MLB disciplinary actions.
  - Steroids Baseball Files, undated (Box 125)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. Press clippings; MLB Joint Drug Prevention and Treatment Program information; Subpoenas; 1950s quiz show scandal ? CRS report; MLB Commissioner internal report; Hearing transcript; Correspondence on MLB steroid use.
  - Steroids Baseball Files, undated (Box 126)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. Rafael Palmeiro test results, slideslow, documents; Interview transcripts; WADA/USADA documents; NBA documents; NBA witness testimony; NFL Coach?s Playbook and Play Safe!; NFL steroid policy documents.
  - Steroids Files, 2007-2008 (Box 132)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. Responses to requests ? TNA, WWE, Aegis, Dr. Ray; WWE test results; Baseball documents produced; Steroid Interviews:; David Black 9-25-07 Dr. Ray 9-24-07; Dixie Carter 12-6-07; Linda McMahon 12-13-07; Stephanie Levesque 12- 14-07; Vince McMahon 12-14-07; Christopher Nitkowski 1-27-08; James Murray 1-31-08.
  - Steroids in Baseball Files, undated (Box 231)
    CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. Baseball-Roger Clemens; McNamee photos; Tejada interview in Baltimore with Mark Tuohey and Phil Schiliro
  - Steroids in Pro Wrestling Files, undated (Box 129)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. SAMHSA/HHS briefing slides & notes; Minnesota/Iowa National Guard documents; USADA requested documents; AEGIS Sciences Corporation requested documents; WWE drug policy information; Press clippings Testing results; Dr. Ray interview notes & transcript; Palmeiro report; Concussion handling procedures.
  - Steroids in Pro Wrestling Files, undated (Box 130)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. WWE Drug Testing Policies; WWE Requested Documents; AEGIS Laboratories Requested Documents; WWE Documents ? Financial Arrangements for Rehabilitation; TNA Talent Policies & Procedures; Committee hearing transcripts - interviews of Frederick Feuerbach, David Black, Tracy Ray.
  - Steroids in Pro Wrestling Interviews, 2007 (Box 134)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. Frederick Feuerbach 9-20-07; Dixie Carter 12-6-07; David Black 9-25-07; Linda McMahon 12-13-07; WWE Financial Statements; WWE Substance Abuse and Drug Testing Policy; Spreadsheets for receipt of WWE drug testing forms; WWE Document Request Responses.
  - Steroids MLB/NFL Files, 2004 (Box 124)
    RESTRICTED: This box is closed until the year 2025. Play Safe ? NFL Youth Football Health and Safety Series; NFL testing policy hearing materials; NFL Guide for Drug Programs Agents; Press clippings; 2004 USA Track & Field Media Guide & Elite Athlete Handbook; MLB Joint Drug Agreement draft.
  - Subpoena Power, undated (Box 230)
    Campaign Financing Investigation; Agency Counsel; Contempt Materials; Tobacco Free Coalition; Badgering witnesses; Models for Subpoena; Contempt- Past Contempt Memorandum; Contempt Resolutions; OGR Campaign Finance 105th; Iran Contra Subpoenas & Rules; Budget and Estimates; Personnel Policies.
  - Tobacco Binders, undated (Box 215)
    Targeting children; Researching the disease; Health effects; Lawyers supervisory.
  - Tobacco Documents, 1994 (Box 209)
    Documents for June 23, 1994, Brown and Williamson Tobacco Hearing.
  - Tobacco Documents, 1994 (Box 210)
    Documents for June 23, 1994, Brown and Williamson Tobacco Hearing; Documents for May 26, 1994, Council on Tobacco Research Hearing; Documents for April 28, 1994, DeNoble Hearing.
  - Tobacco Files, undated (Box 200)
    Advertising for kids; Hearings; Memos.
  - Tobacco Files, undated (Box 201)
    RJR; Joe Camel; Advertising for kids.
  - Tobacco Files, undated (Box 202)
  - Tobacco Files, undated (Box 204)
    Whistleblowers/Letters; Unions; Talking Points; Studies; Coverages; Legislative Proposals; Letters to HAW.
  - Tobacco Files, undated (Box 205)
    A Review of RJ Reynolds Internal Documents (Multiple Copies); Mangini Documents (Multiple Volumes).
  - Tobacco investigations, undated (Box 211)
    Cigarette pack props; Mangini documents volumes I-IV.
  - Video Tapes of Hearings not on C-SPAN, undated (Box 156)
  - Video Tapes on drug pricing, education, nursing home, other reports (non- HAW), undated (Box 154)
  - Video Tapes on drug pricing, education, nursing home, other reports (non- HAW), undated (Box 155)
- Personal Office, (1975-2014); (Boxes 233-278)
  Waxman's personal office files represent his work pertaining to health care reform, environmental matters, and social and financial change, among other important issues. Included are correspondence, press releases, calendars, and printed legislative acts, among others records.
  Box numbers 91, 100, 101, 104, 112, 113, 124, 125, 126, 127, 128, 129,130, 132, 133, 134, 188, 189, 195, 196, 197, 198, 199, 216, 217, 218, 229, 231, and 232 are closed until the year 2025.
  SERIES CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in boxes 243-247 and 253 will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Accepted Invitations, 1985-1995 (Box 234)
  - Accepted Invitations, 1996-2006 (Box 235)
  - Accepted Invitations, undated (Box 277)
    Expired passports.
  - Acid Rain 98th Congress, undated (Box 272)
  - Affordable Care Act Paper Files and Flash Drive, 1990, 2001, 2006 (Box 264)
    Clinton Health Care Reform; Telecommunications Legislation: 1990 digital Audio Tape Recorder Act; 2001 Internal Freedom and Broadband Deployment Act; 2006 Communications Opportunity, Promotion, and Enhancement Act.
  - Calendars, 1975-1990 (Box 275)
  - Calendars, 1991-2014 (Box 276)
  - Clean Air Act, undated (Box 240)
    Waxman correspondence; Dingell correspondence; Waxman Clean Air fact sheets; Waxman Press Releases and Statements; Vice President Quayle's Competitiveness Council.
  - Committee on Oversight and Government Reform, 1998-2005 (Box 265)
    Investigations and Investigative Reports 1998-2005.
  - Correspondence and memos, undated (Box 274)
    Transportation ? Santa Monica Airport; International Trade; Misc. Documents.
  - Correspondence with Administration, undated (Box 258)
    Correspondence with City and State Officials; Correspondence with Foreign Leaders; 'Dear Colleague' Letters.
  - Energy Crisis 2001, 1983-2001 (Box 266)
    Clean Air ? Wilson Administration; 1998 ? Anti-Environment Appropriations Riders; Global Warming 1991-1999; Regulatory Reform 1997-1998; Safe Drinking Water Act 1983-1996; Reagan Administration Anti-Environmentalism.
  - Financial Interest and Syndication Rules, undated (Box 267)
    Vice President Quayle?s Competitiveness Council.
  - Fiscal Year 1982 Budget Reconciliation (Box 260)
  - Generic Drugs - Anti-Competitive Behavior, 1998-2000, 2003, 2004 (Box 249)